{
    "subject": "Nefertiti",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Akhenaten",
    "human_readable": "Nefertiti is married to Akhenaten.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8981513381004333,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the relationship between Nefertiti and Akhenaten?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.886979877948761,
            "question": "Who was Nefertiti married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8078221678733826,
            "question": "To whom was Nefertiti wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7063178420066833,
            "question": "What was the name of Akhenaten's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6601898670196533,
            "question": "Is Nefertiti married to a pharaoh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6530138254165649,
            "question": "Who is Akhenaten?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6479842066764832,
            "question": "What is the name of Nefertiti's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.609087347984314,
            "question": "Were Nefertiti and Akhenaten famous for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.507121205329895,
            "question": "What historical period were Nefertiti and Akhenaten part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3659822642803192,
            "question": "Was Akhenaten associated with any powerful position?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nefertiti is married to Akhenaten.",
            "html": "yago_21892_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical period were Nefertiti and Akhenaten part of?",
            "html": "yago_21892_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were Nefertiti and Akhenaten famous for anything specific?",
            "html": "yago_21892_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Nefertiti's husband?",
            "html": "yago_21892_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21892_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents mention that Nefertiti was the wife of Pharaoh Akhenaten (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21892/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21892/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt), which supports the triple that Nefertiti is married to Akhenaten."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Nefertiti was the Great Royal Wife of Pharaoh Akhenaten, which implies she was married to him."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}